<Root>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://youtu.be/rzArDywPrBY</Exec>
    <Title>Transparent view of a Nacelle</Title>
    <Help>This video provides a travelling view of a nacelle, with transparent walls</Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://youtu.be/8wK1qmRv_l8</Exec>
    <Title>Guided visit to a Wind Turbine</Title>
    <Help></Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://youtu.be/tUse6mSeU-I</Exec>
    <Title>Virtual Wind Farm Tour Ep 5: The Nacelle</Title>
    <Help>This video the preparation stage of an intervention on a Wind Turbine</Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://youtu.be/ZjvBbKqMvEM</Exec>
    <Title>Key concepts of Wind Energy and Wind Turbines</Title>
    <Help>This video presents a short presentation of the basics concepts on Wind Turbines</Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://youtu.be/0bZFwWSccGQ</Exec>
    <Title>Description of one Wind Turbine simulator</Title>
    <Help>This video contains a short introduction to the Simulator for the Wind Turbine with Active Stall control.</Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://youtu.be/UOjPvVjseVc</Exec>
    <Title>START and STOP operations of a Wind Turbine</Title>
    <Help>In this video you can observe the evolution of the Wind Turbine of the Active Stall type, with squirrel cage electric Generator directly connected to the Grid, during two basic operations: START (from disconnected from the Grid to connection, and start production - <i>cutin</i>-), and STOP (from production state to stop state - <i>cutout</i>).</Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://youtu.be/iNcIchrkLNM</Exec>
    <Title>Evolution of the internal signals of a <strong>DFIG</strong> Wind Turbine <strong>wth windgusts</strong></Title>
    <Help>This video presents a detailed analysis of the evolution of several key signals inside a DFIG. <p>It also presents the case of windgusts.</p></Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://youtu.be/zwhvSf7LGbg</Exec>
    <Title>Evolution  of a DFIG during a windgust with problems in the Pitch system - High Wind Speed</Title>
    <Help>This video shows the evolution of the Drive Train  of a 1.5 MW Wind Turbine, with high wind speed, under two different operational conditions: a) normal, and b) with problems in the Pitch system</Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://youtu.be/6pmcnACDfq0</Exec>
    <Title>Evolution of a DFIG Drive Train with wind gusts, and problems in the Pitch System - Low Wind Speed</Title>
    <Help>This video shows the evolution of the Drive Train  of a 1.5 MW Wind Turbine, with low wind speed, under two different operational conditional conditions: a) normal, and b) with problems in the Pitch system</Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://youtu.be/OcR_WvUvN_M</Exec>
    <Title>Management of incidences</Title>
    <Help><i>Incidences</i> are a key concept in Wind Turbines: Wind Turbines are <i>Production Plants</i>, designed to operate in stand-alone mode, adapting their behavior to the changing conditions (wind speed, wind direction, failures in the Grid, internal failures, etc.) <p>Whenever a subsystem is not working properly, or some variable goes out of range, the Wind Turbine's Controller supplies information (incidence) that can be used to analyse the actual condition of the Wind Turbine.</p> <p>Familiarity with the possible <i>incidences</i> in a Wind Turbine <strong>is a must for anyone involved in its Operation and Maintenance</strong>.</p></Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=84BeVq2Jm88</Exec>
    <Title>Erection of a Wind Turbine - MidAmerican Energy -</Title>
    <Help></Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://youtu.be/whTfACs0Og8?t=8</Exec>
    <Title>Use of WindFarmSimulator suite in Minnesota West Technical College</Title>
    <Help>This video by West Technical College presents their installations for Training in Wind Turbine technologies. It shows our WindFarmSimulator in use.</Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7EQa-WZ9c3g</Exec>
    <Title>Construction of Wind Turbine subsystems</Title>
    <Help>Videos showing the construction of different subsystems of a Wind Turbine, notably the Yaw system in the Nacelle.</Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=THf6svHoqaA</Exec>
    <Title>Visit inside a Wind Turbine</Title>
    <Help></Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://youtu.be/Y5T5ZhJQr2o?t=147</Exec>
    <Image>img/stall-vs-pitch-control.png</Image>
    <Title>Wind Turbine Aerodynamics: Stall vs Pitch Regulation</Title>
    <Help>This video shows the difference between the physical principles behind the two most used methods for controlling the intake of power from the wind</Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://youtu.be/rzArDywPrBY</Exec>
    <Title>Transparent view of a Nacelle</Title>
    <Help>This video provides a travelling view of a nacelle, with transparent walls</Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ARd-Om2VyiE</Exec>
    <Title>How a Planetary stage works</Title>
    <Help>The Gearbox of a Wind Turbine have a speed transformation among its axis in the range of 1:60 to 1:125, obtained using several stages. <p>Often the first one is a Planetary stage, connected to the Hub.</p></Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://youtu.be/1-2UVzTvhjc</Exec>
    <Title>Aerodynamic stop during Cut Out of a fixed-pitch Wind Turbine</Title>
    <Help></Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/ghUmhOM81ZY?feature=share</Exec>
    <Image>img/VistaInternaTorreDesplazada.png</Image>
    <Title>Movement of the Tower with high wind, from inside</Title>
    <Help></Help>
  </Video>
  <Video>
    <Exec>https://1drv.ms/v/s!AsEAQ7Uim-DCrchZoQrsXJ9Zq0WcFA?e=qQFMQR</Exec>
    <Image>img/wind-tunnel-experiments-reducido.png</Image>
    <Title>Wind Tunnel Experiments</Title>
    <Help></Help>
  </Video>
  <!-- Puedes añadir más videos aquí -->
</Root>